<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jesper Håkansson]]></title><description><![CDATA[Studies web development. Dart, JS and opensource lover.]]></description><link>https://jesperh.se</link><generator>metalsmith-feed</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 15:16:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jesperh.se/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[OSX backup from Single User Mode]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>I ran into some trouble when I closed my Macbook with a low percentage
of battery left, I had no problem with it whatsoever when I closed it.
The morning after it was turned off, probably because of the low battery.
I tried to start it up and the Apple logo appeared as usually as well as the
loading bar, but it came just till 50 % and no longer. I waited a while to see
if it could load more than 50 % but after a while the computer just turned off.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">OSX backup from Single User Mode</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reactive extensions in Javascript]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>I have done my deep dive in Reactive Extensions, abbreviated called just Rx. And Rx is a library created by Microsoft. It exists in many different languages such as Java, C#, C, Javascript and many other languages. The Javascript version is where I have put my focus.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">Reactive extensions in Javascript</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Material design and React]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Using material design with React is very easy and this blogpost will briefly go through using Material Design in React with material-ui.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">Material design and React</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Using Webpack with hot reload for React and TypeScript]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>JavaScript is growing fast and the build systems evolves. It’s then hard to choose the right tool in this plethora of tools.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">Using Webpack with hot reload for React and TypeScript</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Using Waffle for project management]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>In my project I’ll be using <a href="https://waffle.io/">Waffle</a> for project management. Waffle provides a project management board with an minimalistic interface, unlike other project management boards. It’s not cluttered with stuff that you don’t need and it integrates very well with Github where most of your issues already are present.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">Using Waffle for project management</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Falcor for dart]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://rasmus.eneman.eu">Rasmus</a> and I have for a while been working on to port the
<a href="http://netflix.github.io/falcor">FalcorJS router</a> built by Netflix to Dart.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">Falcor for dart</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Switching from gulp to npm scripts]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>We have been using a large build configuration in our angular application using gulp. Everything  from transpiling ES6, compiling sass, concatenating files and minifying them to trigger live reload. This resulted in a lot of configuration files for each task. Dividing each task into its on file is better than having everything in a tremendous file so this configuration was fine but not the best option for us. The bad truth with this configuration was that one or two people knows how this works (that had set it up once), so that affected the whole team a bit.</p>]]></description><guid isPermaLink="false">Switching from gulp to npm scripts</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>